Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
  - Associated Tile Mfg. Co.
    - Report of interviews with contractors, 1929 Aug.
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries
    - Consumer and dealer investigations on fisheries, 1929 Sept.
    - Investigation on Nordic fish steaks in Syracuse, N.Y., 1938 Jan.
  - Autostrap Safety Razor Co.
    - Dealers and consumers investigation, 1919 Dec.
    - Field investigation, 1921 May-June
    - Notes on safety razor market, 1921 June
  - Bakers of America
    - Order of newspaper ads, undated
    - Advertising plan for War Emergency Council of the baking industry, 1918 Mar. 6
    - Outline of a campaign for Bakers of America, undated
  - Franklin Baker Co. (Baker's coconut)
    - Advertising plan 1923-1927, 1928
    - Account history, undated
    - Investigations
    - Jobbers' answers to questionnaires, 1922 Sept.
    - Rural dealers in Iowa/Illinois/Kentucky, 1928 Apr.
    - Memos, undated
  - Baldwin Piano Co.
    - Consumer investigation, 1930 Jan.
  - Bovril (English beverage)
    - Data, 1927 Nov. 22
  - Burry Biscuit Corporation (see also reel 37)
    - History of Company, 1937 Jan. 7
    - History of educator biscuit (controlled by Burry), undated
    - Proposed trademark, 1937 June 8
    - Radio commercials, 1938 July
    - Radio WRC program, 1938 June
    - Radio WRC program, 1938 Aug.
    - Letter closing account (from Mr. Burry), 1938 Dec. 7
    - Trademarks and photographs, undated
    - Sales figures, 1935-1937
  - Butterick Publishing Co.
    - History of Company, undated
    - Delineator and Everybody's Advertising, undated
    - What we are selling, patterns, 1924 Feb. 28
    - Pattern investigation, 1922 Oct.
    - Office pattern investigation, 1922
    - Users investigation, 1922 July 10-15
    - Pattern investigation by mail, 1923 Nov.
  - William Carter Co. (underwear; see also reels 37, 38)
    - Memos, 1927 May 31
    - Sales figures, 1928 June
    - Infants clothing campaign, 1928 fall
    - Knit underwear investigation, 1925 Sept.
    - Infants underwear investigation, 1929 Jan.
    - Department store investigation (see also reel 38), 1930 Nov.
  - Ceco Radio Tubes (Ceco Manufacturing)
    - consumer investigation, 1930 Feb.
  - Certo (Douglas Pectin Corp.)
    - Teachers' college tests to determine comparative results made with and without Certo, 1926
    - Reports of store demonstrations, 1925
    - Interviews, 1925
    - Mail investigation, 1925 May-July
    - Consumer field investigation, 1925 Sept.
    - Consumer survey, East, 1929 June
    - Consumer survey, West, 1929 July
  - Corning Glass Works
    - Data Steuben glassware (See also reel 38), 1925-1928
  - Durham Derby or Duplex Razor (Enders Razor Co.) (See also reels, 49, 221, 251)
    - Investigations, 1934 Jan.-Mar.
    - Mail investigation, 1936 Dec.
    - Enders razor test, 1937 Apr.
    - Shaving habit survey, 1938 Jan.
  - Dwight Anchor Sheeting (Dwight Manufacturing)
    - Consumer mail investigation, 1925 Sept.
    - Test made by U.S. Testing Co. re: sheets washed 25 times, 1926 fall
    - Tests made by U.S. Testing Co. re: sheets washed 50 times, 1926 fall (Reel 196)
    - Tests on sheets, 1925-1928
  - Easy Washing Machine
    - Plan for market survey, undated
    - Survey, 1938 Jan. 6
    - Summary, 1938 Aug. 26
  - Electrical Industry Sales Conference
    - Report by JWT, 1928 Dec. 4
  - Fleischmann Gin
    - Testimonials, 1936-1937
  - Fleischmann Hydrolyzed Yeast
    - Stox, Vergex, 1926 Mar. 25
    - Office investigation of vegetable stews, 1927 Sept. 25
  - Golden Bear Cookies
    - Consumer and dealer investigations, 1930 Feb.
  - B.F. Goodrich (see also reels 39, 45)
    - Goodrich heavy footwear investigation pre-report, 1928 June
    - Report on consumer and dealer investigation, women's galoshes, 1928 Dec.
    - Analysis of footwear sales, by states, 1930 June
    - Goodrich tire investigation, consumer report, undated
    - Summary of 4 retail dealer surveys, 1932 June
    - Market for storage batteries, 1932 Mar.
    - Plan for analysis of rubber sundries business, 1932 May
    - Preliminary outline of Goodrich sundries problem, 1932 June
    - Log of the Silver Fleet campaign, 1929 Nov. 12
    - Investigation among New York motorists on Silvertown tires, 1930
  - Gorham Company
    - Dealer report, statistical data, trends in living conditions, 1929 Oct.
    - Analysis of 1928 silverware sales by retail shopping areas, 1929 June
    - Consumer recognition of brand names in silver, 1929 Oct.
    - Sales analysis (Gorham), 1930 Feb.
  - Gruen Watch Co.
    - Investigation, undated
  - Richard Hellmann Inc.
    - Field investigation, Hellmann's mayonnaise, 1926 Nov.
    - Hellmann's mayonnaise, questionnaire by mail, 1926 Dec.
    - Blue Ribbon mayonnaise, recipe leaflet, 1927
    - Blue Ribbon mayonnaise, salad ideas, 1927
  - H.P. Hood & Sons, Inc.
    - Organization, 1933 May
    - Analysis of milk division sales, 1933 June
  - International Printing Ink
    - Market investigation, 1930 Jan.
  - Andrew Jergens Co.
    - Consumer investigation, Woodbury soap & Jergens lotion, 1929 Aug.
    - Woodbury's facial soap, trade investigation, 1929 Sept.
    - Conclusions drawn from consumer and trade, 1929 Sept.
    - Investigation and recommendations, 1929 Sept.
    - Conclusions drawn from investigations, 1929 July-Sept.
    - Supplemental sales and advertising analysis, 1929 Oct.
    - Jergens lotion sales analysis 1928-1930, 1930 Apr.
    - Jergens lotion sales figures, 1931 Apr.
    - Jergens lotion sales analysis, 1932 June
    - Nationwide investigation among consumers on use of hand lotion and competing products, 1933 June
    - Analysis of Jergens lotion sales 1932, 1933 May
    - Analysis of Jergens lotion sales in cities of 100,000 and over, 1933, 1934 Mar.
    - Investigation of consumers sending for samples of Jergens lotion, 1934 May
    - Dealer survey on hand lotions in Montreal and Toronto, 1934 July
  - Johnson & Johnson
    - Investigation for market of baby talcum powder, 1924 Oct.
    - Consumer investigation of baby talcum powder, 1925 July
    - Investigation of consumers, dealers, hospitals, physicians, of baby talcum powder, 1926 Oct.
  - Kent-Costikyan (Oriental rugs)
    - Two investigations, East and Midwest, 1921
  - A&M Karagheusian Inc. (Wilton rugs)
    - Investigation on Karagheusian and Herati rugs, 1926 Mar.
    - Sales for Herati and other Wiltons, 1926 Feb.
    - Three investigations on circulation figures, 1926 Apr.
  - Kari-Keen Mfg. Co. (Improved Products Corp., combination auto trunk and baggage carrier)
    - Agreement (unsigned), undated
    - Proposed letter to Sunshine Biscuit Co., 1929 Mar. 28
    - Survey, 1929 May 14
    - Proposed plan for Kari-Keen investigation, 1929 May
    - Kari-Keen questionnaire and factory interview, undated
    - Kari-Keen report on consumer and dealer investigation, 1929 June
  - Lamont-Corliss & Co. (see also reels 49, 52)
    - Peter's chocolate investigation, New York, N.Y., 1922 Apr.
    - Peter's chocolate investigation, Buffalo, N.Y., 1922 Apr.
    - Investigation into typical chocolate milk consumer demands with special reference Peter's, 1922 July
    - Barker's Hasty Lunch cocoa, Fall River, 1926 Oct.
  - Bovril (English beverage)
    - Consumer investigation made by Lehn & Fink, 1928 Mar.
  - New York Office investigations
    - Pertussin (Seecke & Kade), 1931 Jan. 29
    - Bre'r Rabbit molasses/Duff's prepared molasses (Penick & Ford) (see also reel 52): kitchen test on ginger bread, 1932 Mar. 10
    - J&J Colman (USA) Ltd. office investigation on bathing habits (see also reel 38), 1938 Mar.
    - Tints and dyes (Diamond or Tintex), 1937 Nov.
    - Preliminary work on lipstick, 1934-1935
    - Cincinnati Office, 1934
    - Summary of findings on daily use among 1428 women, 1934
    - Letter to Vice President of Northam-Warren, 1934 Dec. 31
    - Report on tests on Cutex, 1935 Jan. 35
    - Report on analgesic effect of Bromo-Seltzer (see also reel 37), 1935 Apr.
    - Consumer and dealer survey on sauerkraut, 1937 Nov.
    - Mail survey, R.T. French (mustard) (see also reel 39), 1937 Dec.
  - Reckitt's (overseas) Ltd., Montreal and Toronto
    - Survey of antiseptic market, 1937 Aug.
  - Lifebuoy soap (Lever Brothers)
    - Report of first Lifebuoy consumer investigation, 1919 Aug. (Reel 197)
    - Report of second Lifebuoy consumer investigation, 1919 Oct. 28
    - Report of third Lifebuoy consumer investigation, 1919 Nov.
    - Report of New York Office investigation, 1919 Dec.
    - Portfolio ads (see also 35mm microfilm reel 16), 1923-1929
  - Martex
    - Consumer report, towels and dealers, 1929 Sept.
  - National Lumber Association
    - Lumber investigation, architects, undated
  - Northam Warren Corporation (Cutex, Odorono) (see also reels 38, 39, 52, 53, 59, 60, 196)
    - Office investigation on Cutex lipstick, 1934 Oct.
    - Office test, crème polish remover, 1935 Apr.
    - Memos and letters, Cutex crème polish, 1935
    - Office test, Cutex, nail aid, 1935 Sept.
    - Office test, Cutex, nail beautifier, 1935 Dec.
    - Investigation on Cutex suntan polish, undated
    - Preliminary summary of cream deodorant test, 1935 Feb.
    - Odorono cream test, 1935 June
    - Cream deodorant test, 1935 Oct.
  - Peace-Dale yarns (J.P. Stevens Co.) (see also reel 52)
    - Consumer and retail investigation, 1920 June
    - Special report on advertising in 1922, 1923 Aug.
    - Report, 1923 May 4
    - Report on yarns in stores, 1926 Sept.
  - Pebeco toothpaste
    - Consumer investigation, 1923 June
    - Dealer or jobber investigation, 1923 June
    - Consumer investigation, 1926 Feb.
  - Penick & Ford (see also reels 52, 196)
    - Bre'r Rabbit molasses test with children, 1933 Aug.
  - J.C. Penney (see also reel 52)
    - Consumer investigation, 1928 July
    - Portfolio ads (see also 35mm microfilm reels 19, 20), 1928-1929
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (see also reel 52)
    - Excursion advertising, 1931 Apr. 28
    - Preliminary test, public attitudes, 1932 Aug.
  - Ed Pinaud
    - Consumer, dealer, jobber field investigations, 1925 Oct.
    - Field investigation on hair tonics, 1925 Dec.
    - Field investigation on toilet waters, 1925 Dec.
  - Pineapple Producers' Cooperative Assn. Ltd.
    - Nutritional value of canned pineapple, undated
    - Comparison price trend, 1931 July-1933 Feb., 1933 Mar.
    - Distributors' holdings of canned pineapple and punches, 1933 Aug.
    - Report, 1933-1934, 1934 Jan. 1
    - Survey of canned pineapple, 1934 Jan.
    - Report for year ending 1934 June 1 and recommendations, 1934 July
    - Analysis of 1926-1927 and 1933-1934, 1934 Aug.
    - Pineapple advertising 1934-1935, 1934 Aug.
    - Additional returns to relation between canned pineapple and pineapple juices, 1935 July
  - Postal Telegraph
    - Preliminary investigation on certain aspects of the postal telegraph service, 1929
  - President Suspender Co.
    - Dealer and consumer investigation, 1924 Jan. 31
  - Rinso (Lever Brothers)
    - Dealer and consumer investigation, 1924 Jan.
  - Royal Baking Powder (Standard Brands) (see also reels 57 and 58)
    - Data book, 1923-1924
    - Data book, 1926-1937
    - Data book, 1928-1937
  - St. Denis bath salts
    - Dealer and consumer investigation, 1929 Sept.
  - Simmons Co. (see also reels 53, 254)
    - Study of price levels, 1932
    - Mail investigation, furniture dealers, 1938 May-June
  - Smokador Mfg. Co.
    - Sales figures, 1924-1927
    - Consumer investigation, 1928 Apr.
  - Society for Electrical Development, Inc.
    - Letter from JWT giving facilities for nationwide research, 1929 Mar. 28
  - Peace Dale Yarns (J.P. Stevens) (see also reels 52, 197)
    - Data book, 1926 (Reel 198)
  - Easy Washing Machine (see also reel 196; this is the clearer copy)
    - Survey, 1938
  - Herbert Tareyton Cigarettes
    - Investigation for Union Tobacco Co., 1928 Dec.
    - Sales analysis, 1928-1929, 1929 June
  - U.S. Food Administration
    - Proposed plan for advertising (by JWT), 1917 Aug. 10
    - Appeals, by JWT, 1917 Nov. 19
    - Letter from N.Y. division of advertising, 1918 Jan. 22
    - Plan to advertise Liberty Loans (by JWT), 1918 Mar. 7
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol
    - Alcorub, 1924 Dec. 6
    - Dealer and consumer investigation, 1924 Dec.
    - Hospital and athletic director investigations, 1925 June
    - Pyro distributors, 1926 Oct.
    - Study of markets for Pyro, 1927 May
    - Anti-freeze investigation, 1928 Nov.
    - Dealer report, 1929 Dec.
    - Consumer investigation, 1930 Jan.
  - U.S. Rubber Co.
    - Lumberman's boots, 1916
    - Artics, 1916
    - Rubbers, 1916
    - Rubber footwear distribution, undated
    - Keds, production charts for 1918 Aug. through 1919 Aug., 1919
    - Regent Keds, production charts for period ending 1919 Dec. 1, 1919
    - Rubber footwear, consumer investigation, 1919
    - Canvas rubber-soled shoes, dealer and consumer, 1919
    - Canvas rubber-soled shoes and footwear, 1920
    - Mississippi delta market, 1921 Feb.
    - Canvas rubber-soled shoes, 1921
    - Dealer and consumer investigation, 1925 May
    - Investigation,, 1925 Apr.-May
  - International Shoe Co. (Chicago Office)
    - Sales etc., 1925 Oct.
    - Analysis of sales, 1925 Oct.
  - Eastman Kodak Co. (see also reel 39)
    - Consumer investigation, 1930 Dec.
  - Vanity Fair Silk Mills
    - Glore silk underwear, 1923 June
  - William R. Warner & Co.
    - Stacomb investigation, 1923 Dec.
    - Check of newspapers for position of advertising, 1924 Feb.
    - Dealer and consumer investigation, 1924 Feb.
    - Sloan's liniment sales and advertising, 1924
    - Sloan's liniment sales and advertising, 1924 fall-1925 spring
    - Sloan's liniment sales and advertising, 1925-1926
    - Sloan's liniment consumer and dealer investigation, 1926 May 17
  - Welch's Grape Juice
    - Investigations, 1928 Feb.
  - Stephen F. Whitman & Son, Inc. (chocolate products) (see also reel 220)
    - Field investigations, consumer comments, 1926 Oct.
  - Thomas Young Nurseries, Inc.
    - Sales to large customers, 1928-1930 (Reel 220)
    - Report on N.Y. market for orchids and gardenias, 1928-1930
  - Bromo-Seltzer (Emerson Drug Co.) (see also reels 372, 196)
    - Sales analysis and figures, 1938 Oct.
    - Bromo-Seltzer copy test by consumer jury, 1938 Dec.
    - Choice of well-known speakers, 1939 Feb.
    - Dealer survey in N.Y. metropolitan area on reaction to Bromo-Seltzer publicity, 1939 Mar.
    - Sales of Bromo-Seltzer and competitive products--Nielsen projects, 1939 Apr.
    - Analysis of newspaper coverage of Bromo-Seltzer seizure in Atlanta, Ga., 1939 Apr.
    - Nationwide dealer survey (remedies recommended), 1939 June
    - Nielsen drug index on sales of Bromo-Seltzer and aspirin products, 1940 May
    - 1935 drug store sales--Drug jobbing areas (cont. in reel 221), 1940 July
  - City Baking Co.
    - A talk on market survey opportunities for the small baker--before Potomac State Baker's Convention, 1939 Jan.
    - Tests made on buns sent over from Rice's bakery, 1939 Feb.-1939 May
    - Test of apple cake, 1939 Sept.
    - Second series of tests on buns, 1940 Feb.
    - Flour and bread consumption trends, 1940 June
  - Dwin-Baldwin Laboratories, Inc.
    - Report #1: general findings and recommendations, 1940 Oct.
    - Report #2: interviews with Dwin wholesalers, 1940 Oct.
    - Report #3: interviews with potential distributors, 1940 Oct.
  - Durham-Duplex Razor Co. (Enders razors)(see also reel 195)
    - Office investigation on razors, 1932 Jan. (Reel 221)
    - shaving cream test, 1932 Aug.
    - Durham-Duplex razor test, 1933 Mar.
    - Survey of consumer buying habits and preferences for shaving preparations, 1933 May
    - Durham-Duplex razor test, 1934 Jan.
    - Durham-Duplex razor investigation, 1934 Mar.
    - Test of new Durham-Derby razors, 1934 Oct.
    - Test among 72 men of new enders razors, 1935 Oct.
    - Consumer investigation on shaving habits, 1936 Feb.
    - Mail investigation among Ender's razor users, 1936 May
    - Enders razor test (mail survey), 1936 Dec.
    - Enders razor test (office survey), 1937 Apr.
    - Test of new style Durham razor, 1937 Nov.
    - Nationwide postcard shaving habit survey among men who have written for Durham razors, 1938 Jan.
  - General Information
    - Guarantees against price declines by manufacturers, 1936 Feb.
    - Drug chain and variety store sales, 1937 July
    - Trend of sales of toilet goods departments in variety chains (first 9 months of 1937), 1937 Nov.
    - Drug store sales in 13 leading areas, 1937 Nov.
    - Leading sales of leading drug chains, 1938 Jan.
    - National advertising revenue, 1938 Feb.
    - Number of customers entering drug stores and variety stores during the year, 1939 Mar.
    - Markets according to urban or rural characteristics, 1938 Oct.
    - List of 106 organizations which employ a large amount of women, 1938 Nov.
    - Wholesale drug sales (radio) (first 9 months of 1937), 1938 Nov.
    - Comparison of two different types of letters tested, 1938 Dec.
    - Easy Washing Machine Corp. mail survey, 1938 Apr.
    - Misc. information on U.S. metropolitan markets--analysis of drug stores' federal income tax, total white families, 1939 Jan.
    - Estimated weekly costs of network programs produced and leading agencies of 1943, 1943 June
  - Proprietary Drug Group
    - Advertising expenditures of 35 proprietary medicines, 1936 May
    - Division of appropriation by media, 1936 May
  - Good Housekeeping Magazine (see reel 49 for April Rochester survey)
    - Magazine advertising effectiveness, 1940 July
    - Memo to Mr. Jaccaci re: interviews with department store executives, 1940 July
    - House-to-house survey on magazine influence, 1940 Aug.
    - Department store survey on magazine influence, 1940 Aug.
    - Comments on the G. surveys with particular reference to the Albany house-to-house survey, 1940 Sept.
  - Grove's Bromo-Quinine
    - Plan for nationwide consumer survey, 1941 Jan.
    - Charts of physicians giving injections, 1941 Mar.
    - Office survey on colds, 1941 Apr.
    - Consumer survey on colds, 1941 Apr.
    - Sales percent of total seltzer aspirin products, 1941 Mar.
  - Dwin-Baldwin Laboratories, Inc. (cont. from reel 220)
    - Report #4: interviews with Dwin retailers, 1940 Oct.
    - Report #5: reports on confidential opinions of Dwin salesmen, 1940 Oct.
  - Johns Manville, Inc. (see also reels 46, 49)
    - Pre-investigation of the market for canopies in N.Y.--supplementary previous report on awnings, 1933 Feb.
    - Investigation of 100 home owners, 1933 Dec.
    - Trade survey and public attitude toward Johns-Manville cedar grain asbestos siding shingles, 1935 Sept.
    - Plan for increasing profits from Johns-Manville buildings materials, 1935 Sept.
  - Martini and Rossi (Vermouth)
    - Consumption (by countries) of sweet vermouth, 1939 Feb.
    - Estimated seasonal sales of soft drinks, 1939 Mar.
    - Notes of meeting on M&R sweet and dry vermouth, 1939 June
    - Italian populations by states in leading cities, 1939 Sept.
    - Total vermouth sales in Pennsylvania, Michigan, and Washington, 1939 Sept.
    - Taste test, 1939 Sept.
    - Investigation among bars and restaurants on serving of Italian vermouth, 1939 Sept.
    - Investigation among Chicago bars on serving of Italian vermouth, 1939 Sept.
    - Consumer survey in 5 cities, 1939 Sept.
    - Price and distribution survey in 20 cities, 1939 Sept.
    - M&R sales in cases, 1940 Mar.
    - Count Rossi vermouth glasses--dealer survey in 4 cities, 1940 May
    - Survey among purchasers of count Rossi vermouth glasses, 1940 May
    - Number of count Rossi vermouth glass orders received from Jan. 1, 1940 to May 31, 1940, 1940 June
    - Survey of vermouth sales in package stores in N.Y., 1940 June
    - Survey of vermouth sales in bars and restaurants in N.Y., 1940 June
    - Taste test--Italian vs. Argentinian vermouth, 1941 Feb.
    - Dealer survey on attitude toward imported and domestic vermouth, 1941 Feb.
    - Sales in 1938 and 1939, 1941 Oct.
    - Plan for price survey of domestic vermouth, 1941 Oct.
    - Dealer and consumer vermouth survey--Boston and Chicago, 1941 Sept.
    - Survey among package stores and cars in N.Y. City, 1941 July
    - Dealer and consumer survey in N.Y. City, 1941 Sept.
    - Revery vermouth survey--dealer, 1941 Dec.
  - Odorono (Northam Warren) (see also reels 52, 53, 197)
    - Test of 4 samples of cream deodorant (K.L.M.N.), 1935 Jan.
    - Two Odorono deodorant powders (present Odorono vs. F.723), 1935 Jan.
    - Office test among 37 women on two deodorant creams, 1935 Feb.
    - Deodorant cream tried for texture, 1935 Mar.
    - Comparison of 1934 and 1935 sales of Odorono, 1935 Mar.
    - Office test on powder deodorant, 1935 Apr.
    - Odorono cream test (C.99.A and C.105.B), 1935 June
    - New deodorant cream test, 1935 Aug.
    - Instant Odorono (F.899.A), 1935 Sept.
    - Cream deodorant test (R.7.A. and R.7.B.), 1935 Oct.
    - Second period of test creams (5.7A and 5.7B), 1935 Nov.
    - Cream deodorant test #669, 1935 Dec.
    - Charts for meeting, 1935 Nov.
    - Test on Odorono Ice, 1936 Apr.
    - Survey on use of body deodorants by men, 1936 Oct.
    - Summary of various surveys made by publications, 1936 Dec.
    - Investigation in the Red Cross drug and department stores in Miami, Fla., 1937 Feb.
    - Odorono cream deodorant and perspiration check, 1935 Aug.
    - Cream deodorant test (F.871.B and f.871.A), 1935 Aug.
  - Pertussin--Seecke and Kade (cough syrup) (see also reel 196)
    - Report of dealer investigation made by Mr. W. Resor, 1933 Oct.
    - Coverage of states by trade magazine schedule, 1934 Feb.
    - Advertising test in Buffalo and Hartford, 1934 Apr.
    - Analysis of sales in stores carrying 2-ounce sizes, 1934 Apr.
    - Study of Pertussin in the South, 1934 Apr.
    - Pertussin trade survey in San Francisco, 1934 Oct.
    - Sales position of Pertussin among leading cough syrups, 1935 Apr.
    - Mail investigation to determine repeat purchases of Pertussin, 1935 May
    - Pertussin dealer investigation on price of Pertussin, 1935 Dec.
    - Mail investigation to determine repeat purchases of Pertussin, 1936 Apr.
    - Trend of sales and relations to advertising and sample distribution, 1938 Mar.
    - Analysis of cough remedy sales in drug stores in the East, 1938 Aug.
    - Sales and advertising season (1937-38 vs. 1936-37), 1938 Oct.
    - Dealer investigation in N.Y. City on cough remedies, 1939 Feb.
    - Survey on preference for Pertussin advertisement, 1940 Sept.
    - Pertussin dealer survey in N.Y. City, 1941 Mar.
  - Planter's Peanuts
    - Analysis of sales, 1933 June
    - Planter's Nut and Chocolate Co.--Outline of information needed, 1933 May
    - Planter's Peanuts distribution check in Royal Scarlet stores in Queens and Nassau counties, 1934 Apr.
    - Analysis of circulation and advertising expenditures for Jan.-Mar. 1934, 1934 Apr.
    - Report covering 6 of the busiest districts in Manhattan, Brooklyn, and Chicago, 1934 May
    - Sales of salted goods (first 4 months of 1933 and 1934), 1934 May
    - Consumer investigation on digestibility of peanuts, 1932 Jan.
    - Sales per m. population (first 10 months of 1934), 1935 Jan.
    - Package test for Planter's Peanuts, 1935 Jan.
    - Distribution and display check in 15 stores, 1935 Feb.
    - Requests for premiums, 1935 Apr.
    - Charts of Planter's distribution in Hartford, 1935 June